Guide to the Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges, Yale College, records
1974-1979
RU 733
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of minutes, seminar proposals, and vitae maintained by Robin Winks while serving on the Yale College Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges.
Yale College (1887- )
Winks, Robin W., 1930-
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-D (YRG 9-D), Records of Yale College committees.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, seminar proposals, and vitae maintained by Robin Winks while serving on the Yale College Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Dormitories; Student housing; Universities and colleges -- Curricula; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Student housing
- Minutes, seminar proposals and Vitae, 1974-1979; Accession 1987-A-093
  - Minutes, seminar proposals, vitae
    - 1974 Jan 8 - Oct 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1974 Nov 4 - 1975 Feb 28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1975 Mar 3 - 1977 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1978 Jan 16 - Sep 28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1978 Oct 2 - Nov 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1979 Feb 1 - Jun 12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1979 Sep 11 - Oct 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1979 Nov 1-27 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1979 Dec 6 - Jun 13 (Box 1, Folder 9)